Welcome to Antipode: DayDreamNight.
This is our Sprint 3 Iteration Overview.
After last week's cross-team evaluation,
we focused on three priorities:
accessibility, internationalisation, and overall UI refinement,
and updated our Kanban accordingly.
From the Settings panel on the Home page, users can now access our new Accessibility & Internationalisation centre.
Screen narration provides spoken feedback for on-screen content.
Subtitles display synchronized text for all audio elements.
High-contrast mode enhances visual clarity with a sharper color scheme.
Users can also fine-tune brightness, contrast, saturation, and playback speed through adjustable parameters.
We also added keyboard support, with Arrow keys for playback control and Control-Arrow keys for quick video actions.
The interface language can now be switched between English and Chinese, and video subtitles support multiple languages.
And all five pages were refined visually for consistency,
especially the Friends page.
We still used GitHub to manage version control
and coordinate collaborative development.
At the end of Sprint 3, we conducted a Cognitive Walkthrough and follow-up interviews to evaluate the updated prototype.
The feedback showed that, despite a few remaining refinements, the core experience is solid and ready for presentation.
This concludes Sprint 3 and finalises our deliverable prototype.
Thank you for watching.