Have you ever wondered what life looks like
on the far side of the Earth?
Welcome to Antipode: DayDreamNight,
a breakthrough social video experience that connects people across day and night
Inspired by antipodes—
two places on Earth that lie directly opposite each other.
On the Home feed, each video captures a real moment from another part of the world,
with a switchable Day–Night mode.
Navigation is intuitive and effortless:
swipe left to skip,
swipe up or down to move between moments,
and swipe right to appreciate and open a creator's profile.
You can also interact naturally: emojis, comment, or share videos with friends.
Creating your own moment is just as seamless.
Switch cameras, record, pause, or save drafts effortlessly.
Add tags, text, and share your perspective with the world.
Stay connected through your Friends feed and expressive user profiles.
Chat brings conversations to life with clear, modern messaging.
On the Profile page, users can explore creators through clean galleries of grids, drafts, and tagged videos.
And to ensure everyone can enjoy the experience…
Antipode supports diverse viewing needs with
screen narration,
subtitles, high-contrast mode and flexible display options.
Users can fine-tune playback with adjustable brightness, contrast, saturation, and speed.
And the interface adapts naturally to different screen sizes.
Keyboard controls make navigation easy on desktop with simple arrow-key shortcuts.
We welcome users from every corner of the world.
The interface and subtitles can switch languages—English or Chinese—for a familiar, comfortable experience.
Antipode opens a new way to experience life across the globe—turning everyday stories into global connections.
Our interactive prototype is complete and ready for presentation.
Thank you for watching.