Welcome to Antipode: DayDreamNight.
This is our Sprint 1 Iteration Overview.
Before Sprint 1 began, we established our core use cases and design concept:
a global video-sharing app connecting people across day and night.
It lets users experience real-time moments from the opposite side of the world.
We planned our development timeline using a Gantt chart,
setting clear weekly milestones.
We also defined team roles and adopted a Kanban workflow.
All project documentation was recorded by Xintong.
To shape the structure and visual direction of the app,
Jiacheng created the initial UI wireframes and prototypes.
In Sprint 1, our primary goal was to build the fundamental page frameworks.
Home Page and Video Player — implemented by Caona,
including the base playback scaffolding.
Capture Page framework — built by Yuanxi,
featuring a front–rear camera switch
and a post-recording flow for adding text,
tags, and basic edits.
Chat and Profile Pages — developed by Ziyi,
forming the foundation of the social interface,
including the basic messaging layout
and user info display.
We used GitHub with feature branches to manage version control
and coordinate collaborative development.
Sprint 1 delivered our core structural frameworks,
but we also identified gaps
pages remain unintegrated, styling is minimal,
and key functions are still incomplete.
These findings shape our priorities for Sprint 2.