Welcome to Antipode: DayDreamNight.
This is our Sprint 2 Iteration Overview.
After Sprint 1, we conducted a heuristic evaluation
to analyse usability issues
Based on these findings,
we updated our Gantt chart and Kanban board
to realign the priorities and workload for Sprint 2 --
focusing on page integration, feature updates,
and unified UI design.
To leverage each member's strengths,
Ziyi shifted to redesigning the Home page,
while Na shifted toward ethics and  testing.
Now, let's look at the updated Sprint 2 interfaces.
Our Home page now supports smooth playback,
reactions, and quick switching.
The Friends page lets users view friends' posts and interact.
The Capture page supports camera switching,
draft preparation and so on.
After recording, users can add tags, and save before posting.
The Chat page provides a cleaner layout for messaging, and group conversations.
The Profile page unifies styling and presents replays,
tagged videos, and activity clearly
We used GitHub with feature branches to manage version control
and coordinate collaborative development.
After sprint 2, we exchanged feedback with another international dev group via soffline demo and a short questionnaire.
These results highlighted gaps in internationalisation, accessibility, and UI styling.
In Sprint 3, we will focus on improving them and completing e
the remaining core interactions.