Have you ever wondered what life looks like on the far side of the Earth?
Welcome to Antipode: DayDreamNight—connecting people across day and night.
Inspired by antipodes—two places directly opposite each other—Antipode brings distant hemispheres together.
On the Home feed, each video captures a real moment from another part of the world, with a switchable Day–Night mode.
Navigation is intuitive: swipe left to skip and swipe right to appreciate and open a creator’s profile.
Swipe up or down to move between moments—traveling across stories with ease.
Creating your own moment is just as seamless.
Switch cameras, record, pause, or save drafts effortlessly.
Add text, tags, and share your perspective with the world.
Stay connected through your Friends feed and expressive user profiles.
Chat brings conversations to life with clear, modern messaging.
On the Profile page, users can explore creators through clean galleries of grids, drafts, and tagged videos.
And to ensure everyone can enjoy the experience…
Antipode supports diverse viewing needs with screen narration, subtitles, and high-contrast mode.
Keyboard controls make navigation easy on desktop with simple arrow-key shortcuts.
Users can fine-tune playback with adjustable brightness, contrast, saturation, and speed.
We welcome users from every corner of the world.
The interface and subtitles can switch languages—English or Chinese—for a familiar, comfortable experience.
Antipode opens a new way to experience life across the globe—turning everyday stories into global connections.
Our interactive prototype is complete and ready for presentation.
Thank you for watching.