Why did no one tell me that New Zealand
was gonna be this cold
I am frozen solid right now
It was about 5 degrees two days ago
I was in a bikini, the weather has changed so much
I knew that the further south
the colder it was gonna be
I didn't know it was gonna be this cold
I'm at the most beautiful lake
we're at Lake Tekapo and
I definitely don't have the right clothing for this kind of weather
I desperately need a pair of gloves because my hands are freezing
Not ready for I came from Sydney summer
And I' m gonna go back to Sydney summer
And I'm not ready
but yeah it's so cold here right now
the weather has changed, we've had some really gorgeous days
I mean when the sun's out and it's blue skies
I'm happy anyway, I just wish I was more prepared, I'm so cold